The method environment has to be added to all of the other type rules in our
方法环境必须添加到我们的
system. This is really easy to do, because only the dispatch rules actually care
系统。这真的很容易做到，因为只有分派规则才真正关心
about what the methods are. All the rest of the rules just pass the method environment
关于方法是什么。所有的睡觉规则都只是通过方法环境
along. So what do I mean by that? Well, here's our rule for add, with
一起去吧。我这么说是什么意思？嗯，这是我们的加法规则，
just the object environment. So now what were going to do, is we're going to add a
只有对象环境。所以现在我们要做的是，我们要添加一个
method environment. And the sub-expressions will be just type checked.
方法环境。子表达式将只进行类型检查。
In exactly the same method environment as the entire expression and all the other rules
在与整个表达式和所有其他规则完全相同的方法环境中
simply pass down the method environment from the root towards the leaves
简单地将方法环境从根传递到叶
without changing it just as in this rule. Now it turns out that for some cases
而不像这条规则那样改变它。现在事实证明，在某些情况下，
involving self-type, we actually need one more thing in our environment. And so, the
涉及到自我类型，我们实际上在我们的环境中还需要一样东西。因此，
actual full environment for Cool type checking consists of three things. First of
Cool类型检查的实际完整环境由三部分组成。第一个
all, there's the mapping O, that gives types to object IDs. There's this mapping
All，有一个映射O，它为对象ID提供类型。有一张地图
M, that gives types to methods. And finally, we just need to know the name of
m，它为方法提供类型。最后，我们只需要知道
the current class. So, whatever class the expression we're type checking actually sits
当前类。因此，我们正在进行类型检查的表达式实际位于哪个类
in. So the full form of a sentence in the Cool type checking [inaudible] looks like
在……里面。因此，Cool类型检查[听不见]中句子的完整形式如下所示
this And is read as follows, under the assumption that the object identifiers
在假设对象标识符
have the types given by O. That the methods have the signatures given by M And
具有由O给出的类型。这些方法具有由M和M给出的签名。
that the expression sits in the class C. Then we can prove that the expression E has
表达式属于类C，那么我们可以证明表达式E具有
the type T. And here's an example, the ad example, the, the rule for addition again,
类型T，这里有一个例子，广告例子，再加一次的规则，
written out with the full environment. So the rules that I've given
写下了完整的环境。所以我给出的规则
you for type checking here are cool specific and some other languages have very
您在这里进行类型检查是很酷的，其他一些语言有非常
different rules. But there are some general themes in type checking. First of
不同的规则。但是在类型检查中有一些一般性的主题。第一个
all, type rules are defined on the structure of expressions. So they're typically
所有类型规则都是在表达式的结构上定义的。所以他们通常是
done in this inductive fashion, where the types of an expres-, the type of
以这种归纳的方式来完成，其中表达的类型-，表达的类型
an expression depends on the types of its sub expressions. And also the types of variables
表达式取决于其子表达式的类型。以及变量的类型
and more generally any free names in an expression, things like method
更广泛地说，表达式中的任何自由名称，如方法
names, they're going to be modeled by an environment, so we're going to have some mapping
名称，它们将由环境建模，所以我们将有一些映射
sitting around that's going to tell us any kind of fr-. A Russian what assumptions
坐在那里会告诉我们任何类型的fr-。一个俄国人有什么假设
the type rules should make about the types of those names And one thing
类型规则应该对这些名称的类型做出规定，而且还有一件事
you've probably noticed by now but it's worth saying explicitly is that type
您现在可能已经注意到了，但是值得明确说明的是这种类型
rules are really very compact. The notation is not complicated but there's actually
规则真的很紧凑。符号并不复杂，但实际上
a lot of information in these rules. I mean you have to take some time to
这些规则中包含了很多信息。我的意思是你得花点时间
sit and read them carefully to really understand what they are saying.
坐下来仔细阅读，才能真正理解他们在说什么。